marathi.tv 2018-01-30

# Privacy Policy - Marathi.TV

**Marathi.TV  Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in EU & US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy & cookie policy carefully below to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

Any time you visit  _Marathi.TV_ , our servers will automatically record information gathered from your browser, like your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, exit pages, referring pages, date/time stamp, time spent on each page, and number of clicks. We use this information to customize your user experience by personalizing content, appropriately fulfilling your service requests, informing you of updates to the web site and our services that may be of relevance to you, and letting you know about any new offers that you might be interested in. 

When signing up for our newsletter, ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you visit pages on our site, register or subscribe to our newsletter, accept our cookie consent, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?  **

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

 **•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

 **•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

 **•**  To personalise content, ads and track user data

 **What are ‘cookies’?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes, we do use cookies for analytics, tracking purposes & to make this site work properly.

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

 **Third Party Disclosure**

We reserves the right to disclose users’ profile information, including both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information, when required to do so by law or at the request of a trusted third party. You also acknowledge and consent that we can disclose any information you provide if we, in our sole discretion, believe that this disclosure is (1) in compliance with federal, state, municipal, and/or any other legal regulations, including requests from representatives of law enforcement, or any other legal process (regardless of whether or not disclosure is required by the applicable law); (2) defend or safeguard Marathi.TV’s, or a third party’s, property or legal rights; or (3) protect the health and safety of you or another person.

 **Third party links**

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

ü  Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website or other websites.

ü  Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

ü  Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **We have implemented the following:**

 **•**  Remarketing with Google AdSense

 **•**  Google Display Network Impression Reporting

 **•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

 **•**  DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

 **•**  We use regular Malware Scanning.

 **•**  We do not use an SSL certificate

 **•**  We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers.

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

 **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email – contact.marathitv@gmail.com

 **•**  Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

 **If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at contact.marathitv@gmail.com**

and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.
